minimalisti.com 2017-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Minimalisti.com Interior design and Architecture Magazine

At www.Minimalisti.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received by Minimalisti.com and how it is used.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Minimalisti.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Minimalisti.com allows its advertising partners (Google Adsense and Glam Media) to use cookies and web beacons on our site to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice visit the NAI at http://www.networkadvertising.org. To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Minimalisti.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-partyad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Minimalisti.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Minimalisti.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
